// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is correct about features of JavaScript?",
    answer: "All of the above.",
    options: [
      "JavaScript is a lightweight, interpreted programming language",
      "JavaScript is designed for creating network-centric applications",
      "JavaScript is complementary to and integrated with Java.",
      "All of the above."
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string?",
    answer: "substring()",
    options: [
      "slice()",
      "split()",
      "substr()",
      "substring()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following function of String object creates an HTML anchor that is used as a hypertext target?",
    answer: "anchor()",
    options: [
      "anchor()",
      "link()",
      "blink()",
      "big()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following function of Array object represents the source code of an object?",
    answer: "toSource()",
    options: [
      "toSource()",
      "splice()",
      "toString()",
      "unshift()"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which built-in method returns the calling string value converted to lower case?",
    answer: "toLowerCase()",
    options: [
      "toLowerCase()",
      "toLower()",
      "changeCase(case)",
      "None of the above."
    ]
  },
   {
     numb: 6,
     question: "Which built-in method returns the length of the string?",
     answer: "length()",
     options: [
       "length()",
       "size()",
       "index()",
       "None of the above."
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 7,
     question: "Which of the following function of String object combines the text of two strings and returns a new string?",
     answer: "concat()",
     options: [
       "add()",
       " merge()",
       "concat()",
       "append()"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 8,
     question: "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as a subscript, as if it were in a <sub> tag?",
     answer: "sub()",
     options: [
       "sup()",
       "small()",
       "strike()",
       "sub()"
     ]
    },
   {
     numb: 9,
     question: "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as a subscript, as if it were in a <sub> tag?",
     answer: "join()",
     options: [
       "concat()",
       "join()",
       "pop()",
       "map()"
     ]
   },
   {
     numb: 10,
     question: "Which built-in method reverses the order of the elements of an array?",
     answer: "",
     options: [
       "changeOrder(order)",
       "reverse()",
       "sort(order)",
       "None of the above."
     ]
  },

];